ED]
Oops.
Oh, sorry.
Wear gaster wareis
pleas
cel dumb
th
Please.
Yes, I am.
Hello.
I'm Sei Fukumura, the leader of Morning Musume。 23 leader, Sei Fukumura.
I've come here today with an announcement for Ms. Inoue.
Haruka Inoue, Morning Musume。 25th anniversary audition,
25th anniversary audition!
Congratulations!
You have been chosen to join Morning Musume。ヌs 17th term!
How do you feel now?
I am happy, but I am both happy and anxious.
Why did you audition for Morning Musume。 Why did you audition for Morning Musume。
I liked them and thought they were cool,
I want to be cool too.
Then I decided to become a member of Morning Musume。 What do you want to do now that you have decided to join Morning Musume。
I love to sing, so I want to express that love and become someone that many people can see.
What do you want to do with the members of Morning Musume。 Do you have anything you would like to do with the members of Morning Musume。
Anything is fine. Like going to live shows.
I have a longing to be in an outdoor concert, so I would like to do an outdoor concert.
Morning Musume。 We have performed at many outdoor live concerts, so let's work hard together and take lessons together.
I look forward to working with you.
Yes, thank you very much.
You did a great job.
Thank you very much.
Let's do our best.
I am Haruka Inoue, a 17-year-old high school sophomore from Kyoto.
I have some anxiety, but I will try my best to be positive.
Thank you very much.
Hello. I am the leader of Morning Musume。 I am Sei FUKUMURA, the leader of Morning Musume。
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
I've come here today with an announcement for Yumigeta-san.
Yumigeta Akko, you have passed the Morning Musume。 25th anniversary audition!
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
You have been selected to join Morning Musume。ヌs 17th term.
How do you feel now? How do you feel now?
I'm really happy. Thank you very much.
I'm sure you've gone through a lot of auditions so far, how was it?
I've been to a lot of auditions before.
It's different from lessons and auditions. I'm really happy because I've been working hard with only one thing in mind: to get in.
Thank you very much. Now that you have decided to join Morning Musume。
What do you want to do now that you have decided to join Morning Musume。
I am really looking forward to joining Morning Musume。 I will do my best as a member of Morning Musume。
I look forward to working with you.
How old are you?
I'm 14.
You are 14 years old and 165 centimeters?
Yes, I am.
Big!
You're a big guy.
So you're going to use your height and style to your advantage?
I hope you can use your height and style to make a lot of success in Morning Musume。 Please use your height and style to play a big role in Morning Musume。
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm Ako Yumishita, a 14-year-old junior high school student from Shizuoka Prefecture.
I want to give a performance that will convince people that I was chosen.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Ontine in Daisy Solution. No one can solve it.
Even you, older than me, can't do it now
I can't tell you who all of this is mine.
Yes, we have two accepted this time, sir.
Yes, sir!
Wait, they're both too nervous.
You two were working so hard together, taking lessons and all.
Yes, we've been accepted as new members of the 17th term.
So, we are the same age.
Yes, we are.
What do you think?
We passed the exam together.
It's reassuring.
Reassuring.
How's that?
It's reassuring.
So you two are good friends?
We're good friends.
I'm so nervous. Are you okay?
Your shoulders are really stiff.
I'd like to get to know you both better from now on,
I'd like to get to know them better, and I'd like to meet the other members of Morning Musume。 I'd like to meet the other members of Morning Musume。
I would also like to take pictures with them.
Do you think you can do it?
Go for it.
You think you can do it?
Yes, I'll do my best.
You think you'll do well?
Then let's get going.
Yes, I'm going.
I'm off.
This is the fifth time I've announced my acceptance in person,Face to face, this will be the fifth time I am announcing my acceptance in front of him like this,
This is the fifth time for me to present my acceptance in front of the audience, and the last time for me to welcome a new member,
Both of them are new members from the general public, so this is the first time I have met them,
My first impression of Haruka Inoue is that she is the type of girl who would do this when she makes eye contact with me,
My first impression was that Haruka Inoue is the type of girl who would look at me like this when we make eye contact, so I thought she might be a little shy,
But even at this moment, I could tell that she was an interesting girl,
I hope that I will be able to reveal more and more of her personality and her true brightness.
I also got the impression that Ayako Yumokeda has a cheerful personality.
She is very quick and cheerful, and I think she must have gone through a lot of auditions.
Also, her name is very distinctive, so I am looking forward to seeing what her nickname will be,
I would like to talk about that when I meet the members again.
I would like to talk about it when I meet the members again. Sta.
Now let's meet the new members again!
I told everyone in advance that we would meet the new members on this day, so I didn't mean it as a surprise.
How do you feel now? Well, first of all, I'd like to welcome our new member.
Yes, I have the same feeling that I had exactly one year ago.
Please listen to my memories.
I was so thrilled to be the first junior member, so I want to get to know them well.
I'm also very happy to have more friends as a member of Morning Musume。 I'm very excited to see what kind of girls will be joining us as Morning Musume。
I'm excited! I'm so excited! So much!
And for the 12th term, we are accepting new members for the second time.
No matter how excited I am, they will come in 10 minutes later.
Again!
But I'm looking forward to working together with you.
I'll be waiting for you.
Next time, next time!
I see.
Now, I'd like to invite a new member to join us.
Please welcome our new member.
He's cute.
Cute.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Haruka Inoue, a 17-year-old high school sophomore from Kyoto.
I look forward to working with you.
Nice to meet you.
I am Reine Inoue, a 14-year-old junior high school student from Shizuoka Prefecture.
I look forward to working with you.
So, two from the general public!
Congratulations!
Now, how do you feel about meeting the members?
I want to hear!
I am very happy. It's nice to meet you.
They are so cute!
It's even bigger than it looks in the video.
I'm so happy.
The cutest! The cutest!
Let's keep asking questions from the members!
I hear you, members.
Keep asking questions.
Okay, Rinu-chan.
I want to ask you about your special skills.
I know it's not very good quality,
I sang Finnish Minion as a special skill at the audition.
That's great. What kind of Finnish Minion?
Can you do it now?
Can you do it?
Please try to sing it.
I'm looking forward to hear you sing now.
What about you, Nakamura?
There is a famous dance in Shizuoka called Chakkiri-Bushi.
I've never done it before, even though I'm from Shizuoka.
Show me.
I want to run.
On the "se-no, shi-no-u".
Please do.
Congratulations.
Nice. You showed us with song and dance.
Yes.
Morning Musume。 I would like to know your favorite song of Morning Musume。
I like "Over the Time and Over the Sky,
I also like Young Lord.
Roman My Dear Boy,
I also like The Peace.
It's so cute.
I want to be the best.
Who is your favorite senior or someone you admire?
Okamura-san.
Thank you very much.
The first one.
Sakura Oda.
Nice to meet you.
I was wondering what you two are called.
Like it's a long time ago.
Sometimes they call me by my toddler name.
Haru-chan.
Haru-san.
Haru-san?
I know what you mean.
My friends call me
They call me "geta geta".
Geta geta, which means "to be bad at something" or "to be bad at something".
How do you feel about the future?
For your fans
I'm looking forward to it.
I have many seniors whom I admire.
I would like to do my best
I would like to do my best.
As a member of Morning Musume。 As a member of Morning Musume。As a member of Morning Musume。 As a member of Morning Musume。
Don't just look at the fun things.
I will do my best not only to have fun, but also to look away from the hardships
I will do my best.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Now that I have heard a lot about you two, I would like to go to the photo shoot.
We will continue to work hard as a 14-member team, so please give us your support.
I'm scared.
I'm scared. When are they coming? It's been a while.
I'm nervous. I'm rather nervous.
But I'm looking forward to it.
Excuse me.
Good morning.
Eh? It's been a while.
How long has it been?
Good morning.
Miss me?
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work today.
Thank you very much.
Did you have a good time?
It was fun.
Are you full of energy today?
Yes, I am.
I see.
I came here today to talk to you, Hanyu-chan,
It has been decided that she will join as a new member of ANGELUM.
Congratulations, Okun!
Yesterday, I watched Eiwahi with Angeleum's "Let's meet and be loved.
Thank you.
Why were you watching?
I happen to watch the seniors' stuff all the time,
I thought they were so cool yesterday, so I watched them again.
Thank you.
How are you doing?
I'm fine.
Am I dreaming?
It's real.
Congratulations!
All right. You okay?
I'm glad.
You're so cute. I knew it.
Wait a minute.
Thank you.
This is super duper hard.
That's amazing.
Thank you very much.
What do you think? It's a little avant-garde, maybe,
It's kind of avant-garde, but it's okay?
I'm glad.
We're finally at the starting point.
Yeah, that's right.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
I'm the one, I'm the one, but I'll be gone in about a month,
I know I don't have much time left, but please take care of me until the end.
I don't know what it feels like.
I know, right? I'm sorry. I came on such short notice.
It's okay. I'm happy.
Happy? I'm glad.
I'm Hana Goto, the newest member of Angeleum. I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm so happy, that's what I've been feeling all of a sudden,
I was anxious about when I would be able to make the starting point,
I was worried about when I would be able to make a start,
I was worried about when I would be able to make a start, but now that you told me this, I feel like I am in a better place,
I also thought that I would like to do my best to be like the members I have admired so much.
I was really overwhelmed by the girl who was even more amazing than I had imagined.
I had an image of her being very energetic, but she talked all the time,
She talked all the time,
I thought she was really full of energy,
I am really looking forward to seeing Ange in the future,
There was no one like Hana-chan yet,
I think she will bring a new wind to Ange, and I'm really looking forward to seeing her.
I'm really looking forward to it. Sta.
I'm really looking forward to seeing her. STE!
Halo! Ste.
Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Come here, Kyou.
Let's eat sushi together.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's eat sushi.
What do you like?
Eggs.
Let's have an egg.
Let's eat together.
Okay, I'll crack it open.
Okay.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
Can I eat it?
Yes, I can.
Let's eat.
I'll eat.
Do you want to talk first?
I'll talk first.
You want to eat first?
Yes, go ahead.
Well, I'd like to tell you something first,
Um, Mikio.
Yes, Mikiho.
We've decided that you're going to join us as a new member of ANGELUM!
Congratulations!
A new member.
Really?
Really.
It's a surprise, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
He's so cute.
You're so cute.
What's that?
Congratulations.
I don't know anything.
Um, I'm Ange.
Are you Yukyo-chan?
Yukyo-chan is Angstrom.
I'm Angulum?
Yes, that's right. I'm Angulum.
What? Why? Really?
Really. That's why we came here. Today.
It's great.
Thank you for coming such a long way.
No, no, no, no.
What?
Isn't it great?
Really?
See, the manager is here, too.
Then it's real.
Yay!
We did it!
Ha-ha-ha!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Please, it's nice to meet you too.
A-ha-ha!
That's great!
I'm glad to hear that.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
ah-ha-ha-ha
Are you okay?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Let's work together.
I'll do my best!
I'm Yukiho Shimoitani, a 16-year-old high school sophomore from Okayama Prefecture, and the newest member of Angeleum.
I'm so surprised that I can't come up with words even more than usual.
I'm really happy. I know I have a lot to learn.
I'm sure I have a lot to learn, but I'm going to do my best so that when I perform in front of the audience, I'll be in perfect condition.
It was more interesting than I expected. I thought she was really cute and I'm really looking forward to seeing more of her.
I thought she was really cute, and I'm really looking forward to seeing her in the future.
I'm really looking forward to seeing what she can do in the future, even if I'm just talking to her for a minute.
I'm really looking forward to it. I'm already Ange.
Tôi sẽ vacuum
Now hhhhhhhhhh
This is what I'm doing; it's the second time I've done it.
I'm always nervous and then nervous.
You know, this one day is going to change my life forever.
I thought about that, and I thought I have to chat all day today.
It was a performance test.
I was really nervous to perform in front of so many customers by myself.
I was really nervous.
There were times when I wondered if I could handle it.
But I got a lot of support from the fans
I got a lot of letters and stuff like that.
I was really determined to do my best.
My friends were cheering me on.
So I watched the show.
I haven't met my teacher yet.
I'm going to junior high school in a little while.
The rest is here. I'm going to go.
I'll report back to you.
Good morning.
I saw the award for best half-over.
Sorry. My face flew a little.
Were you nervous?
Yes, I was.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you.
Miki Kawashima, you have been selected as a new member of JuiceJuice. Thank you very much.
How do you feel now? You seem to be calm. Yes, I am.
Project since I became a trainee.
Project, so I've been working hard to make my debut with Hello! Project, so I'm very happy.
I'm very happy. What was your impression of JuiceJuice?I am very happy. What was your impression of JuiceJuice?
I think their performances are really cool and their songs are a bit mature.
Miki, do you think you are good at matured style or this kind of genre?
I don't know if I'm good at adult-oriented music, but I want to try it.
I want to try. I'm glad to hear that. Then, JuiceJuice is perfect for you. I got the impression that you have a real sparkle in your eyes,
I was also impressed by the way your eyes sparkle, and I thought you were so majestic, so I'm looking forward to seeing how you will perform once you join JuiceJuice,
My first impression of her is that her eyes sparkle even when she is live.
I am really looking forward to the future, and I ask for your continued support as JuiceJuice.
I'm very happy to be joining JuiceJuice.
I am Miho Kawashima, a 15-year-old first-year high school student from Kyoto.
This is the second time for me to welcome a new member as a leader.
I had an idea of what it would be like.
But she was quite calm and cool as she talked about her current feelings.
I thought that she was very confident and open, even outside of the performance.
I'm getting more and more curious about what kind of girl she is.
I really want to see Mihu on stage as soon as possible.
I also want to see you talking with her backstage and so on.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I never thought I would be able to join the band.
I'm so happy!
Juice Juice has a mature and cool image.
I want to improve my singing and dancing, and try my best to fit in as soon as possible.
I'll do my best to become a person who can shine in front of you all as soon as possible.
I was so surprised!
It's easy to understand what you really feel.
I'm so happy!
Good morning.
Good morning
Please, have a seat.
Yes, why did you come here today?
Memories of Nakano Sun Plaza.
Memories, yes.
But first, I have something to say to you.
I have something to say to you.
Hinoha Yoshida, I'd like to tell you that you're going to be a member of Halo Pro trainee unit 2 and 3.
I'd like to tell you that you're going to join Halo Pro Trainee Unit 2 and 3.
I wish you the best of luck.
Thank you very much
I didn't think I'd get in now.
I'm very happy to be able to be a little bit closer to my debut.
I am very happy.
I'm sure that the activities will be a bit more practical from now on.
I wish you the best of luck.
I hope that you will be able to improve your existing skills
I hope that you will do it.
Yes, ma'am.
Excuse me. Good morning. Pleased to meet you.
Please sit down.
Please, come in. I don't know why I'm here today.
Well, goodbye, Nakano Sun Plaza community. Community. Before that, I have something to tell you.
Rena Kamimura, you are
You've been accepted to join Halo Pro trainee unit 2 and 3.
Thank you very much.
I'm so surprised. I love the performances of the trainee unit.
I really like the performances of the trainee unit members, and I'm worried that I'm going to drag them down.
I'd like to cooperate with you all and do my best, and I'll never give up on my dream.
Hello! Ste, why did you call me here today?
Before I start taking comments, I would like to tell you something.
I'd like to tell you that we've found some new members in trainee units 2 and 3.
I think we've found a new member for trainee units 2 and 3.
I'd like to go see him earlier today, so please join me in welcoming him.
Members, please.
Is he here?
Open your eyes, please.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm Hinana Yoshida.
Pleased to meet you.
Yes, please.
Actually, there's one other person.
Excuse me.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What's your name, please?
Tomimura.
Yes, ma'am.
Excuse me.
Trainees Units 2 and 3 will now have seven trainees.
I'd like them to work even harder.
Yes, sir.
And one more thing...
I have one more announcement.
I have an announcement.
These seven students will be
Next year, we're going to start a new Hello! Project's new group.
And we've decided to be a part of it.
That means seven of us will be making our debut together.
Ladies and gentlemen, gather around. Gather around, gather around.
We'll spend the next year deciding on the group's shape.
We'll decide on the timing of the group's debut next year.
What exactly do you mean by deciding on a form?
Well, this year marks the 25th anniversary of Hello Project.
Hello Project will be celebrating its 25th anniversary this year.
We're going to be holding auditions for the 25th anniversary of Hello Project.
If we find a suitable member for the new group...
And if we find a new member who fits in with the group...
So, this diagonal...
This diagonal is the starting member.We've decided to make you the starting members.
We will continue to strengthen our unity and create our own group.
We will further deepen our unity and create our own group form.
We will build a new group from the ground up.
I am sure that you will come again.
We have two new members, and the seven of us will be working together for the time being.
I hope that the seven of us will be able to work together for the time being and get the group back on track.
That's all for me. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.